[He must want me to go to see the Old Madam]
[EP04]
Who are you?
I'm your wife,
Su Muwan.
Save my mother.
Young Marshal,
Young Madam only has external injuries.
As long as she takes good care of herself,
she'll be fine.
But she's too weak.
She must take
the tonic.
Got it.
Why are you so pale?
Young Marshal,
it's not proper
to hit her now.
Get out.
Young Marshal,
what about the medicine?
Put it here.
Where's my mother?
She's safe.
Drink the medicine first.
I want to see her.
You're not in a position to make demands.
As long as you behave yourself,
she will be safe.
This is my last act of kindness
to the Su family.
You're using my mother as a hostage.
Young Marshal,
here's the medicine from Young Master Chu.
He said it's useful for Young Madam.
You can get more if you need.
He's waiting for you in the study.
He also said...
What?
Chu Nanfeng said
if the Ling family doesn't take good care of her,
he can take her away at any time.
Deputy Li,
boil this Chinese medicine
three times for her,
and make sure she takes it all.
Without my permission,
she's not allowed to go out.
Yes, sir.
Ling Shenxing,
you're really ruthless,
threatening me with my mother.
Gosh, the medicine in the Republic of China is so bitter.
I've been looking for you for a long time.
It turns out you've come to someone else's house.
Young Marshal.
Ling Shenxing,
if everyone knows the Old Marshal is dead,
let's see if you can
keep your position.
The Old Marshal's disappearance
has caused a sensation.
But I heard that he was killed.
If so,
I'm afraid you're too young
to take over
the position of the Marshal.
Yeah.
My father went on a long journey.
But he came back yesterday.
He's right next door.
But
he caught a cold
and is indisposed.
Young Marshal,
forgive me.
We must
see the Old Marshal today.
Otherwise,
we won't be able to sleep.
Yeah.
We want to see the Old Marshal.
Where is he?
We must see him today.
He's dead.
How can you make him alive?
The Marshal is coming.
How is it possible?
It's impossible.
Father.
Ling Shenxing.
What do you mean?
Are you just brushing us off like this?
Since ancient times, filial piety has been valued.
How dare a young marshal
find someone to impersonate his father?
If this gets out,
your position as young marshal
may not be secure.
I want to see if you are real or fake.
Old Marshal.
It's really the old marshal.
What's going on?
I saw him dead with my own eyes.
Since you've seen the Old Marshal,
I'll
take my leave.
Forgive me.
I wonder if Miss Su knows
how brave and resourceful her man is.
I'll tell Lord Chu
that his son
is longing for a woman
and should get married.
Young Marshal,
the Old Marshal's twin brother
is impersonating him at the casino again.
My gambling uncle?
Then bring him here.
Remember,
I want a trustworthy uncle.
Yes, sir.
Uncle,
since you love to impersonate my father
and swindling,
then you should play my father well.
As for your daughter Xueqiu,
as long as you behave yourself,
I will take good care of her.
Miss Ye,
please go to see the Old Madam.
It's about the Young Madam.
I'm not interested in
the fight between women.
My body heals
three times faster than a normal person.
It seems that in the novel, I can only get hurt,
but not die.
It's impossible to leave this world by death.
Since I can't leave,
I'll just live well.
Su Muwan and I are really fated.
Even the birthmark on our backs is the same.
Miss,
the clothes for washing.
Cuijuan,
where's my mother?
We haven't heard from her yet.
What about Hongxiu?
Miss,
I heard that Hongxiu
went home to visit her family.
Don't worry about her.
Young Marshal promised to keep her safe.
Since he said that,
he won't break his promise.
That's why
I dare not act rashly.
Mom,
since God gives me another chance
to be with you,
I will never let you get hurt again.
Cuijuan,
help me get changed.
OK.
Did I like wearing these clothes?
Miss.
You said that making clothes is like being a person.
You should be vigorous
and brilliant like a bunch of flowers.
Miss.
You are noble
and the most beautiful woman in Yang City.
The line of your suitors
reaches all the way to the West.
Chu Nanfeng, Young Master Chu
is particularly devoted to you.
Everyone in Yang City knows that.
Was I really like that?
Of course.
You were
the most famous socialite.
After you went out,
the Young Marshal saved you from the wild cats.
You fell in love with him at first sight,
and did everything you could
to make the Sus spend half of their fortune
on this marriage.
Everyone else is jealous of you.
Seeing that he doesn't like you,
they...
His original fiancée
is actually
Miss Ye, Jinrou.
No wonder.
Oh, right.
Well,
buy everything on this list
for me.
Yes,
My Lady.
This is the tonic sent from the kitchen.
What?
A faint bitter taste.
Although this prescription has many spices
and hawthorn,
but it smells different from ordinary tonics.
It seems that the person behind this
has ulterior motives.
Who sent you?
Did you also go to see my mother?
Young Madam, you really make a scene.
Fuyuan,
if someone doesn't know,
they might think you've brought
great honor to our Ling residence.
You fake your death,
lose your memory every day,
making us a laughingstock in Yang City.
Please.
The Old Madam is waiting for you.
Then how much honor have you brought to us?
As long as I live here,
I'm your young madam,
your master.
[Fuyuan is a prominent maid]
[by the Old Madam's side.]
[But when a maid saw her,]
[she didn't look respectful,]
[but exchanged glances.]
[There must be something wrong.]
Young Madam, why is your dress wet?
[He deliberately wet my dress.]
[in a disgraceful way.]
[The Old Madam in the novel pays the most attention to rules.]
[If I go like this,]
[I'll get into trouble again.]
[But you]
[have underestimated me.]
I want them to know me again.
Su Muwan.